<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GIPO</title>
    <link>http://www.gipo.tw/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GIPO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gipo.tw/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://www.gipo.tw/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 14:57:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gipo.tw/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Grand Intellectual Property Office (GIPO) started-up at Taipei City, and has worked in the field of patent, trademark prosecution and other legal cases for more than ten years. As a rapidly grown company, our goal is to provide our clients with the most professional and the highest quality service, as well as minimized costs. We work only on projects which can be conducted by us with high level of competence expected by clients, and obtain many excellent praises and evaluations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advantage</title>
      <link>http://www.gipo.tw/en/advantage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 14:57:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gipo.tw/en/advantage/</guid>
      <description>I. MORE THAN 10 YEARS OF SUCCESS GIPO has an excellent team including patent attorneys/patent agents, and is the best in the field of patent specification/claim drafting, trademark prosecution/litigation and other IP-related areas.
II. EXCLUSIVE SERVICE AND REASONABLE SERVICE FEE Patent attorneys/patent agents in GIPO always discuss technical features with clients and conduct specification/claim drafting themselves, and offer the best services and reasonable service fee to you.
III. PROFESSIONAL TEAMS Since GIPO handles every case professionally and employs open management, many in-house patent and R&amp;amp;D engineers are pleased to collaborate with our patent attorneys/patent agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fee Schedule</title>
      <link>http://www.gipo.tw/en/fee-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 14:57:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gipo.tw/en/fee-schedule/</guid>
      <description>GIPO handles IP-related cases such as patent/trademark prosecution, licensing, and appraisal services, and offers flat fee services that are transparent and reasonable. Our customized flat fee includes everything from filing, patent drawings, to office actions and invalidation actions. Please contact us via telephone or Email.
 TEL：+88625172340 Email：service@gipo.tw  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Reach Us</title>
      <link>http://www.gipo.tw/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 14:57:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gipo.tw/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>WE ARE LOOKING FORWARD TO YOUR MESSAGE
Do you have questions or require individual counseling? Just contact us without any obligations.
You can reach us via telephone from Monday to Friday between 9:00 a.m. and 7:00 p.m. You can schedule consultation appointments with our reception or patent attorney you wish to speak to. Of course, we will take your wishes into consideration when scheduling the meetings. This is why meetings are also possible outside regular business hours and at your premises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://www.gipo.tw/en/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 14:57:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gipo.tw/en/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Many people focus on the development of Intellectual Property right, and many law firms or patent/trademark offices were established. Some of them have common quality with high prices. Others do not charge high prices but with bad quality. However, do you know what firm is suitable for you?
According the concerns above, GIPO expects to provide the best quality with reasonable prices and the most effective services to our clients. We adhere to the highest standards of excellence and integrity to fulfill our clients’ IP objectives, and strive to exceed our clients’ expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>